And now we're going to go over Fireball.
Fireball is a very long-standing staple of the red series of this game.
It is X and a red, much like Blaze.
However, Fireball is a little different.
Fireball is a Sorcery, but you may pay the X damage and have it deal to a single creature or play.
However, Fireball has the extra added thing that you may deal damage to multiple targets.
So you would divide that damage evenly among the targets, but you also have to pay one additional colorless Mana for each additional target.
So, if you were targeting two things you would have to pay one colorless and the red, and then you would start counting Mana for the X.
Likewise with two, three, and so forth.
But, you've also got to realize that that X divided evenly, rounded down amongst the number of targets.